

# Daniel Índias

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER AGILE PROBLEM-SOLVER

## Contact

- Schultz gate 10, 0365 Oslo
- daniel.indias@gmail.com
- +48 504 606 969

## Skills

\_\_\_\_\_

\_\_\_\_\_

Software Development

**Technical Problem-Solving** 

**Customer Service** 

Operations Optimization

## **About**

Skilled and adaptable software developer. Five years of experience in freelance programming, specialising in Python, JavaScript, Angular, React and database technologies. Proven track record of delivering good quality code and solutions to a diverse range of clients. Fast learner with a strong desire to contribute technical expertise. Looking for a remote parttime software development role.

## Education

Master in Business Administration

**ISCTE Business School** 

**ERASMUS** International Management (Berlin)

Bachelor of Science in Biology (Major)

Faculdade de Ciências da Universidade de Lisboa

Minor in Computer Science

## **Professional Experience**

Fiverr, Upwork

2019 - Present

#### Freelance Programmer

- Proficient in Python, JavaScript, Angular, React, and various database structures and languages.
- Demonstrated ability to deliver high-quality code and solutions to meet client needs.

**Indie Campers** 

2017 - 2019

#### **Depot and Logistics Management**

 Oversaw customer service, optimized operations, and managed depots on-site from 2017 to 2019.
Transitioned to a freelance role post-2019, providing on-demand availability and placement in specific depots as needed by the company.

Gour.Media

2014 - 2017

#### Marketing and IT Consultant

 Collaborated with numerous public and private clients, including Pipedrive, Generali, L'Oréal Group, Second Home, Navigator, and Medinfar Sorológico, among others.